contentking.eu 2011-06-23

# Privacy Policy - ContentKing - Free High Quality Articles for your Site!

Contentking.eu respects the privacy of its users and does not collect any personally identifiable user information without prior notice. Web statistics are the sole and private property of Contentking.eu and are only used for troubleshooting purposes. 

Contentking.eu generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. When you register to become a member of Contentking.eu and subscribe to our services, you are asked to provide information, such as your e-mail address, name and/or other information. 

Contentking.eu uses this information to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to any of our newspapers, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice 

We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs. 

We may allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance or forums and job search software, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. Contentking.eu does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. 

Contentking.eu may use cookies to keep some information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your own computer. We use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliated companies. 

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and click stream information. 

If you don't want cookies stored on your computers, your Web browser would likely include an option that allows you to not accept cookies. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of Contentking.eu may not function properly. 

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 10. Contentking.eu is not intended for use by minors or children, especially those under age 18. No one under age 18 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and/or chats. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardians(s) before using our services, including registration and/or subscriptions to our services offered by this site. 

If your children disclose information about themselves in our public discussion areas, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Contentking.eu cannot be held responsible for any action by your children while using our services, with or without your consents. 

This is the website of Contentking.eu. We can be reached via e-mail at info<at>contentking.eu. The email address has been encoded as such for security reason. Please replace "<at>" with @. 

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time without any prior notice to the visitors. Continued access of Contentking.eu by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. It is the goal of Contentking.eu to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.
